Guide to the Robert Giard Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Robert Giard papers
1972-2002
YCAL MSS 702
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
50.34
(271 boxes)
The papers consist of photographs, correspondence, diaries, financial papers, and printed materials documenting Robert Giard's career as a photographer and personal life, spanning the years 1972 to 2002. The bulk of the papers contain photographic prints by Giard in several sizes of various subjects, including portraits of gay and lesbian writers, landscapes, nudes, still lifes, and portraits of the Thanks Be To Grandmother Winifred Foundation grant recipients.
Giard, Robert, 1939-2002
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Jonathan G. Silin on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 2004. Gift of Jonathan G. Silin, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Associated Materials
Printed material received with the collection was removed for separate cataloging and can be accessed by searching the library's online catalog.
Robert Giard (1939-2002)
Robert Giard was an American photographer, born in Hartford, Connecticut in 1939. He received a Bachelor of Arts from Yale University in 1961, and Master of Arts in Comparative Literature from Boston University in 1965. In 1972 he began to take photographs, focusing on landscapes and portraits of his friends, artists, writers, and nudes. His monograph Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers, published by MIT Press in 1997, contains a selection from over 500 portraits he had taken in the previous decade. In 1996, Giard was commissioned to document the 321 grant recipients of the Thanks Be To Grandmother Winifred Foundation. The grant recipients were women over the age of 54 whose projects benefitted adult women. From 1996 to 2001, Giard traveled across the U. S. to photograph each year's grant recipients. He died in 2002 of a heart attack.
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of photographs, correspondence, diaries, financial papers, and printed materials documenting Robert Giard's career as a photographer and personal life, spanning the years 1972 to 2002. The bulk of the papers contain photographic prints by Giard in several sizes of various subjects, including portraits of gay and lesbian writers, landscapes, nudes, still lifes, and portraits of the Thanks Be To Grandmother Winifred Foundation grant recipients.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: I. February 2005 Acquisition, 1972-2002. II. October 2011 Acquisition, 1988-2001.
Gay authors -- United States -- Portraits; Lesbian authors -- United States -- Portraits; Photographers -- United States -- Archives; Older women -- United States -- Portraits; Photographic prints; Photographers -- United States -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Giard, Robert, 1939-2002; Thanks Be to Grandmother Winifred Foundation
- February 2005 Acquisition, 1972-2002; 1; 50.06; (270 boxes)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Jonathan G. Silin on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 2004.
  Arrangement
  This group of material is organized into five series: Correspondence, Professional Papers, Photograph Work Prints, Oversize Photographs (16" x 20"), and Photographs (11" x 14").
  Scope and Contents
  This group contains correspondence, professional papers diaries, financial papers, photographs, printed material, journals, and other related papers.
  Box 271 contains print-outs of original inventories of 16" x 20" photographs. These inventories contain detailed information not found in this finding aid and originate from a data export of a FileMaker Pro Database acquired with the collection.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 765.
  - Correspondence
    - Personal and professional correspondence including articles on gay writers, publishers, and artists; clippings; postcards and mailings, 1972-2002; 13 (Box 1)
    - Personal and professional correspondence including articles on gay writers, publishers, and artists; clippings; postcards and mailings, 1972-2002; 11 (Box 2)
    - Personal and professional correspondence including articles on gay writers, publishers, and artists; clippings; postcards and mailings, 1972-2002; 10 (Box 3)
    - Personal and professional correspondence including articles on gay writers, publishers, and artists; clippings; postcards and mailings, 1972-2002; 10 (Box 4)
    - Personal and professional correspondence including articles on gay writers, publishers, and artists; clippings; postcards and mailings, 1972-2002; 6 (Box 5)
  - Professional papers
    - Miscellaneous diaries and notebooks chronicling Giard's early involvement with photographic ideas and interest in literature, interspersed with news clipping, literary quotes, sketches, 1977-1986; 6 (Box 5)
    - Papers pertaining to Thanks Be to Grandmother Winifred Foundation project, extensive travel notes, and descriptions of the meetings and photographic sessions with the 250 grant recipients, circa 2002; 4 (Box 5)
    - Papers pertaining to Thanks Be to Grandmother Winifred Foundation project, extensive travel notes, and descriptions of the meetings and photographic sessions with the 250 grant recipients, circa 2002; 6 (Box 6)
    - Complete set of photocopies of Giard's original diaries related to the Gay and Lesbian Writers Series, photocopies describing meetings and photographic sessions with the writers (original diaries are in the permanent collection of the New York Public Library), 1985-2001; 4 (Box 6)
    - Desk files, weekly calendars, grant proposals, resumes, professional correspondence, exhibition announcements and brochures, obituaries, awards, articles, plans for future projects, 1997-2002; 8 (Box 6)
    - Desk files, weekly calendars, grant proposals, resumes, professional correspondence, exhibition announcements and brochures, obituaries, awards, articles, plans for future projects, 1997-2002; 18 (Box 7)
    - Desk files, weekly calendars, grant proposals, resumes, professional correspondence, exhibition announcements and brochures, obituaries, awards, articles, plans for future projects, 1994-2002; 16 (Box 8)
    - Desk files, weekly calendars, grant proposals, resumes, professional correspondence, exhibition announcements and brochures, obituaries, awards, articles, plans for future projects, 1980-2002; 15 (Box 9)
    - Desk files, weekly calendars, grant proposals, resumes, professional correspondence, exhibition announcements and brochures, obituaries, awards, articles, plans for future projects, 1997-2002; 18 (Box 10)
    - Desk files, weekly calendars, grant proposals, resumes, professional correspondence, exhibition announcements and brochures, obituaries, awards, articles, plans for future projects, 1997-2002; 17 (Box 11)
    - Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers, book dummies, undated; 15 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous teaching lecture notes, photo reference material, film data sheets, undated; 2 (Box 13)
    - Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers, documents related to publication of Giard's monograph including permission forms, research notes, essay drafts, reviews and listings, and cover layouts, undated; 14 (Box 14)
    - Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers, documents related to publication of Giard's monograph including permission forms, research notes, essay drafts, reviews and listings, and cover layouts, undated; 16 (Box 15)
    - Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers, documents related to publication of Giard's monograph including permission forms, research notes, essay drafts, reviews and listings, and cover layouts, undated; 5 (Box 16)
    - Gay & Lesbian Writers Series, project research material sorted by geographical areas, 13 (Box 16)
    - Gay & Lesbian Writers Series, project research material sorted by geographical areas, 17 (Box 17)
    - Gay & Lesbian Writers Series, project research material sorted by geographical areas, 7 (Box 18)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1987; 9 (Box 18)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1987; 14 (Box 19)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 15 (Box 20)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 14 (Box 21)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 16 (Box 22)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 3 (Box 23)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 17 (Box 24)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 12 (Box 25)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 14 (Box 26)
    - Giard's financial records, 1984-1992; 13 (Box 27)
    - Work journals, 8 (Box 27)
      Extensive printing notes and diagrams including burning, dodging, toning, developing instructions, printing dates
    - Work Journals, 21 (Box 28)
    - Printed material, 6 (Box 28)
    - Printed material, 37 (Box 29)
    - Particular Voices, cover, 1 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous printed material, 7 (Box 30)
  - Photograph Work Prints
    Organized into five subseries: Gay and Lesbian Writers, Landscapes, Nudes, Portraits, and Miscellaneous.
    - Gay and Lesbian Writers
      - Men
        - Gay #1 (A-D), 13 (Box 31)
        - Gay #1 (A-D), 17 (Box 32)
        - Gay #1 (A-D), 15 (Box 33)
        - Gay #2 (E-H), 9 (Box 34)
        - Gay #2 (E-H), 11 (Box 35)
        - Gay #2 (E-H), 12 (Box 36)
        - Gay #2 (E-H), 10 (Box 37)
        - Gay #3 (I-K), 11 (Box 38)
        - Gay #3 (I-K), 12 (Box 39)
        - Gay #3 (I-K), 8 (Box 40)
        - Gay #4 (L-M), 13 (Box 41)
        - Gay #4 (L-M), 10 (Box 42)
        - Gay #4 (L-M), 10 (Box 43)
        - Gay #4 (L-M), 9 (Box 44)
        - Gay #4 (L-M), 7 (Box 45)
        - Gay #5 (N-R), 9 (Box 46)
        - Gay #5 (N-R), 8 (Box 47)
        - Gay #5 (N-R), 10 (Box 48)
        - Gay #5 (N-R), 10 (Box 49)
        - Gay #6 (S-U), 8 (Box 50)
        - Gay #6 (S-U), 7 (Box 51)
        - Gay #6 (S-U), 9 (Box 52)
        - Gay #6 (S-U), 8 (Box 53)
        - Gay #7 (V-Z), 9 (Box 54)
        - Gay #7 (V-Z), 10 (Box 55)
        - Gay Book and Others #1 (A-H), 10 (Box 56)
        - Gay Book and Others #1 (A-H), 14 (Box 57)
        - Gay Book and Others #1 (A-H), 14 (Box 58)
        - Gay Book and Others #1 (A-H), 11 (Box 59)
        - Gay Book and Others #1 (A-H), 12 (Box 60)
        - Gay Book and Others #2 (I-Z), 10 (Box 61)
        - Gay Book and Others #2 (I-Z), 8 (Box 62)
        - Gay Book and Others #2 (I-Z), 9 (Box 63)
        - Gay Book and Others #2 (I-Z), 10 (Box 64)
        - Gay Book and Others #2 (I-Z), 8 (Box 65)
        - Gay Book and Others #2 (I-Z), 9 (Box 66)
      - Women
        - Lesbian #1, 9 (Box 67)
        - Lesbian #1, 7 (Box 68)
        - Lesbian #1, 7 (Box 69)
        - Lesbian #1, 6 (Box 70)
        - Lesbian #1, 7 (Box 71)
        - Lesbian #2, 7 (Box 72)
        - Lesbian #2, 7 (Box 73)
        - Lesbian #2, 7 (Box 74)
        - Lesbian #2, 6 (Box 75)
        - Lesbian #2, 6 (Box 76)
        - Lesbian #3, 11 (Box 77)
        - Lesbian #3, 10 (Box 78)
        - Lesbian #3, 9 (Box 79)
        - Lesbian #3, 7 (Box 80)
        - Lesbian #3, 9 (Box 81)
        - Lesbian #3, 6 (Box 82)
        - Lesbian #4, 8 (Box 83)
        - Lesbian #4, 7 (Box 84)
        - Lesbian #4, 9 (Box 85)
        - Lesbian #4, 9 (Box 86)
        - Lesbian #5, 12 (Box 87)
        - Lesbian #5, 10 (Box 88)
        - Lesbian #5, 7 (Box 89)
        - Lesbian #6, 13 (Box 90)
        - Lesbian #6, 8 (Box 91)
        - Lesbian #6, 10 (Box 92)
        - Lesbian #6, 3 (Box 93)
        - Lesbian Book #1, 9 (Box 94)
        - Lesbian Book #1, 8 (Box 95)
        - Lesbian Book #1, 8 (Box 96)
        - Lesbian Book #1, 8 (Box 97)
        - Lesbian Book #1, 8 (Box 98)
        - Lesbian Book #1, 9 (Box 99)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 19 (Box 100)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 9 (Box 101)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 8 (Box 102)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 9 (Box 103)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 10 (Box 104)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 8 (Box 105)
        - Lesbian Book #2, 9 (Box 106)
      - Groups
        - Group Men #1, 9 (Box 107)
        - Group Men #1, 9 (Box 108)
        - Group Men #1, 10 (Box 109)
        - Group Men #1, 14 (Box 110)
        - Group Men #1, 5 (Box 111)
        - Group Men #2, 11 (Box 112)
        - Group Men #2, 17 (Box 113)
        - Group Men #2, 9 (Box 114)
        - Lesbian, 8 (Box 115)
        - Lesbian, 7 (Box 116)
        - Lesbian, 13 (Box 117)
        - Lesbian, 12 (Box 118)
        - Lesbian, 17 (Box 119)
        - Lesbian, 13 (Box 120)
        - Lesbian, 10 (Box 121)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Activists #1, 13 (Box 122)
        - Activists #1, 13 (Box 123)
        - Activists #2, 11 (Box 124)
        - Gay Assorted, 24 (Box 125)
        - Gay Assorted, 24 (Box 126)
        - Gay Assorted, 23 (Box 127)
        - Mixed Miscellaneous #1, 36 (Box 128)
        - Mixed Miscellaneous #2, 8 (Box 129)
        - Mixed Miscellaneous #2, 17 (Box 130)
    - Landscapes
      - Landscapes, 36 (Box 131)
      - Landscapes, 35 (Box 132)
      - Landscapes, 40 (Box 133)
      - Landscapes, 7 (Box 134)
      - Gay Sites, 11 (Box 135)
      - Dark Series, 20 (Box 136)
      - Dark Series, 29 (Box 137)
    - Nudes
      - Nudes #1, 28 (Box 138)
      - Nudes #1, 26 (Box 139)
      - Nudes #1, 21 (Box 140)
      - Nudes #1, 19 (Box 141)
      - Nudes #1, 10 (Box 142)
      - Nudes #2, 24 (Box 143)
      - Nudes #2, 23 (Box 144)
      - Nudes #2, 13 (Box 145)
      - Nudes #2, 18 (Box 146)
      - Nudes #2, 10 (Box 147)
      - Figures in Landscapes, 26 (Box 148)
      - Figures in Landscapes, 19 (Box 149)
      - Figures in Landscapes, 22 (Box 150)
      - Figures in Landscapes, 16 (Box 151)
    - Portraits
      - Self-Portraits, 4 (Box 152)
      - Thanks Be To Grandmother Winifred
        - Winifred #1, 9 (Box 153)
        - Winifred #1, 10 (Box 154)
        - Winifred #1, 7 (Box 155)
        - Winifred #2, 10 (Box 156)
        - Winifred #2, 6 (Box 157)
        - Winifred #2, 5 (Box 158)
        - Winifred #2, 3 (Box 159)
        - Winifred #3, 14 (Box 160)
        - Winifred #3, 13 (Box 161)
        - Winifred #3, 12 (Box 162)
        - Winifred #3, 11 (Box 163)
        - Winifred #3, 14 (Box 164)
        - Winifred #3, 7 (Box 165)
        - Winifred #4, 9 (Box 166)
        - Winifred #4, 10 (Box 167)
        - Winifred #4, 13 (Box 168)
        - Winifred #5, 11 (Box 169)
        - Winifred #5, 12 (Box 170)
        - Winifred #5, 12 (Box 171)
        - Winifred #5, 12 (Box 172)
        - Winifred #5, 10 (Box 173)
        - Winifred #6, 5 (Box 174)
        - Winifred #6, 23 (Box 175)
        - Winifred #6, 16 (Box 176)
        - Winifred #6, 20 (Box 177)
        - Winifred #6, 20 (Box 178)
        - Winifred #6, 13 (Box 179)
        - Winifred #6, 23 (Box 180)
        - Winifred #6, 12 (Box 181)
        - Winifred #7, 11 (Box 182)
        - Winifred #7, 7 (Box 183)
        - Winifred #7, 8 (Box 184)
        - Winifred #8, 8 (Box 185)
        - Winifred #8, 7 (Box 186)
        - Winifred #8, 7 (Box 187)
        - Winifred #8, 7 (Box 188)
        - Winifred #8, 10 (Box 189)
        - Winifred #8, 12 (Box 190)
        - Winifred #8, 12 (Box 191)
        - Winifred #8, 12 (Box 192)
        - Winifred #9, 25 (Box 193)
        - Winifred #9, 29 (Box 194)
        - Winifred #9, 22 (Box 195)
        - Winifred #9, 20 (Box 196)
        - Winifred #9, 29 (Box 197)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Particular Voices, 36 (Box 198)
      - Particular Voices, 7 (Box 199)
      - Particular Voices, 7 (Box 200)
      - Particular Voices, 6 (Box 201)
      - Particular Voices, 7 (Box 202)
      - Assorted and tone, 13 (Box 203)
      - Assorted and tone, 10 (Box 204)
      - Assorted and tone, 36 (Box 205)
      - Assorted and tone, 26 (Box 206)
      - Assorted and tone, 8 (Box 207)
  - Oversize Photographs (16" x 20")
    Organized into four subseries: Gay and Lesbian Writers, Landscapes, Portraits, and Nudes.
    - Print-outs of original inventories of 16" x 20" photographs. Inventories contain detailed information not found in this finding aid and originate from a data export of a FileMaker Pro Database acquired with the collection., 5 (Box 271)
    - Gay and Lesbian Writers
      - Male
        - Abbott, Franklin, 1992 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0024
        - Abbott, Steve, 1988 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0255
        - Adair, Peter, 1994 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0379d
        - Alarcon, Francisco X., 1994 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0089e
        - Albee, Edward, 1991 July (Box 208)
          GLW# 0016d
        - Albee, Edward, 1991 July (Box 208)
          GLW# 0102c
        - Albee, Edward, 1991 July (Box 208)
          GLW# 0106c
        - Albee, Edward, 1991 July (Box 208)
          GLW# 0107
        - Aletti, Vince, 1993 May (Box 208)
          GLW# 0442a
        - Alfaro, Luis, 1994 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0098f
        - Alyson, Sasha, 1988 July (Box 208)
          GLW# 0306d
        - Ameen, Mark, 1987 August (Box 208)
          GLW# 0119c
        - Barker, Elver, 2001 August (Box 208)
          GLW# 0233e
        - Barnett, Allen, 1988 December (Box 208)
          GLW# 0556d
        - Bentley, Eric, 1986 August (Box 208)
          GLW# 0372
        - Berger, Maurice, 2000 June (Box 208)
          GLW# 0214d
        - Berube, Allan, 1994 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0075e
        - Bidart, Frank, 1987 September (Box 208)
          GLW# 0130c
        - Bidart, Frank, with Reflection in Mirror, 1987 September (Box 208)
          GLW# 0131c
        - Blackberri, 2001 July (Box 208)
          GLW# 0230d
        - Boone, Bruce, 1988 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0248c
        - Boone, Bruce, 1988 January (Box 208)
          GLW# 0249c
        - Borawski, Walta, 1987 September (Box 209)
          GLW# 0126e
        - Borgman, C.F. (with stuffed gorilla), 1987 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0526c
        - Borgman, C.F., 1987 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0527c
        - Boswell, John, 1987 (Box 209)
          GLW# 0095
        - Boyd, Malcolm, 1989 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0582a
        - Brainard, Joe, 1990 March (Box 209)
          GLW# 0630e
        - Brainard, Joe, 1990 March (Box 209)
          GLW# 0631d
        - Bram, Christopher, 1988 October (Box 209)
          GLW# 0549d
        - Bronski, Michael, 1987 September (Box 209)
          GLW# 0125b
        - Broughton, James, 1988 December (Box 209)
          GLW# 0553d
        - Bumbalo, Victor, 1987 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0519f
        - Call, Hal, "At the Circle.. .", 1999 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0185e
        - Callen, Michael, 1987 September (Box 209)
          GLW# 0113c
        - Cameron, Peter, 1999 May (Box 209)
          GLW# 0196d
        - Campo, Raphael, 1992 March (Box 209)
          GLW# 0042f
        - Cashorali, Peter, 1989 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0595c
        - Cashorali, Peter with Leland Hickman Text, 1989 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0596a
        - Chauncey, George, 1991 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0474d
        - Chesley, Robert, 1989 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0558
        - Chin, Justin, 1999 January (Box 209)
          GLW# 0187d
        - Clarke, Kevin, "At The...", 1988 June (Box 210)
          GLW# 0294c
        - Cooper, Dennis, 1986 November (Box 210)
          GLW# 0513d
        - Cooper, Dennis, 1986 November (Box 210)
          GLW# 0514b
        - Cooper, Dennis, 1986 November (Box 210)
          GLW# 0515c
        - Cooper, Bernard, 1989 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0589c
        - Corn, Alfred, 1987 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0522c
        - Corn, Alfred, "With D...", 1987 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0523c
        - Cox, Christopher, 1989 August (Box 210)
          GLW# 0608c
        - Crimp, Douglas, 1985 (Box 210)
          GLW# 0365b
        - Crimp, Douglas, "Chez...", 1985 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0366b
        - Crimp, Douglas with..., 1986 May (Box 210)
          GLW# 0367
        - Crimp, Douglas, 1986 May (Box 210)
          GLW# 0368b
        - Crimp, Douglas, 1986 May (Box 210)
          GLW# 0369c
        - Crisp, Quentin, 1986 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0359
        - Crisp, Quentin, 1986 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0360c
        - Crowley, Mart, "At Gate...", 2001 July (Box 210)
          GLW# 0227g
        - Cuadros, Gil, 1996 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0667f
        - Cunningham, Michael, 1991 December (Box 210)
          GLW# 0020
        - Curzon, Daniel, 1988 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0272a
        - D'Allesandro, Sam, 1988 January (Box 210)
          GLW# 0274a
        - De Larverie, Storme, 1999 November (Box 211)
          GLW# 0205e
        - Delaney, Samuel R., 1987 March (Box 211)
          GLW# 0547a
        - Denneny, Michael, 1988 July (Box 211)
          GLW# 0300a
        - Dixon, Melvin, 1988 October (Box 211)
          GLW# 0320d
        - Dixon, Melvin, 1988 October (Box 211)
          GLW# 0321
        - Donaldson, Stephen, 1992 June (Box 211)
          GLW# 0051d
        - Doty, Mark, 1992 May (Box 211)
          GLW# 0044
        - Duberman, Martin, 1987 February (Box 211)
          GLW# 0544
        - Duplechan, Larry, 1988 January (Box 211)
          GLW# 0280
        - Dureau, George, 1992 February (Box 211)
          GLW# 0061e
        - Dureau, George, 1992 February (Box 211)
          GLW# 0393a
        - Ellenzweig, Allen, 1988 July (Box 211)
          GLW# 0299
        - Ellenzweig, Allen, "Man in a Striped Shirt", 1980 November (Box 211)
          GLW# 0699
        - Elmslie, Kenward, 1990 May (Box 211)
          GLW# 0466b
        - Escoffier, Jeff, 1989 January (Box 211)
          GLW# 0577
        - Feinberg, David B., 1989 March (Box 211)
          GLW# 0601
        - Ferro, Robert, 1985 November (Box 211)
          GLW# 0351
        - Field, Edward, 1987 September (Box 211)
          GLW# 0115
        - Finn, William, 1993 January (Box 211)
          GLW# 0428
        - Fisher, Salih Michael, 1988 December (Box 211)
          GLW# 0555a
        - Fishman, Israel David, 1989 June (Box 212)
          GLW# 0150
        - Ford, Charles Henri, at the Dakota, 1989 October (Box 212)
          GLW# 0614
        - Fouratt, Jim, 1994 January (Box 212)
          GLW# 0386
        - Fox, John, 1987 January (Box 212)
          GLW# 0516
        - Fox, John, 1987 January (Box 212)
          GLW# 0517
        - Fox, John, 1987 January (Box 212)
          GLW# 0518
        - Friedman, Sandford, 1989 December (Box 212)
          GLW# 0621
        - Fries, Kenny, 1994 June (Box 212)
          GLW# 0335
        - Gambone, Philip, 1990 June (Box 212)
          GLW# 0470
        - Garber, Eric, 1989 January (Box 212)
          GLW# 0564
        - Gilgun, John, 1988 January (Box 212)
          GLW# 0273
        - Ginsberg, Allen, with His Own Portrait of Burroughs, 1986 May (Box 212)
          GLW# 0370a
        - Ginsberg, Allen with Altar, 1986 May (Box 212)
          GLW# 0371
        - Giorno, John (Burrough's Bunker), 1993 March (Box 212)
          GLW# 0431
        - Glickman, Gary, 1987 February (Box 212)
          GLW# 0525
        - Glines, John, 1987 March (Box 212)
          GLW# 0539
        - Glines, John, with Portrait of Mother, 1987 March (Box 212)
          GLW# 0540
        - Gluck, Robert, 1985 November (Box 212)
          GLW# 0356
        - Gluck, Robert with Politically Incorrect Figures, 1997 September (Box 212)
          GLW# 0679
        - Goldstein, Richard, 1993 June (Box 212)
          GLW# 0445
        - Gooch, Brad, 1986 February (Box 213)
          GLW# 0361a
        - Greco, Stephen, 1987 February (Box 213)
          GLW# 0538
        - Grimsley, Jim, 1992 January (Box 213)
          GLW# 0026
        - Grumley, Michael, 1985 November (Box 213)
          GLW# 0354
        - Gunn, Thom, 1988 January (Box 213)
          GLW# 0270a
        - Gunn, 1988 January (Box 213)
          GLW# 0271
        - Gunnison, Foster, 1992 October (Box 213)
          GLW# 0421a